Guide to the Stanford University, Registrar's Office, records SC1288
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, 1891-1999; Series 6 (Accession ARCH-2013-027)
  - From Math. 129 to end Spr. 27-23 (re-filmed on R. 30), 25 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarter Reports (Phys. Ed. Hygiene), 1927-1928; 26 (Box 1)
  - 2. Summer Quarter Reports, 1927-1928; 26 (Box 1)
  - 3. Advanced Senior Qtr. Reports, 1928; 26 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anatomy-English), 1928-1929; 26 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports (Geology-Zoology), 1928-1929; 26 (Box 1)
  - 6. Spring Quarter Reports, 1928-1929; 26 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. ll - Zool.), 1928-1929; 27 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1928-1929; 27 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1928-1929; 27 (Box 1)
  - 4. Senior Reports Spring, 1928-1929; 27 (Box 1)
  - 5. Summer Quarter Reports (Rom. Lang. B240 Espinosa), 1928-1929; 27 (Box 1)
  - 1. Summer Quarter Reports (Rom. Lang. - B260 Espinosa), 1928-1929; 28 (Box 1)
  - 2. Med Reports, 1926-1929; 28 (Box 1)
  - 3. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1929-1930; 28 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1929-1930; 28 (Box 1)
  - 5. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1929-1930; 28 (Box 1)
  - 6. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1929-1930; 28 (Box 1)
  - 1. Senior Reports June, 1929-1930; 29 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1929-1930; 29 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1929-1930; 29 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Quarter Reports, 1930; 29 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Gr. Arts)(Germ. Lang. Pg. 1- Rohden), 1930-1931; 29 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports (German Lan. P. 2-Rohden), 1930-1931; 30 (Box 1)
  - 2. Sum 1926-1927 refilmed from R. 24 Chem 12-Chem128) (Spr. 1927-1928 Refilmed from R25 Math. 129 - Phys. Ed. 1, 30 (Box 1)
  - 3. Autumn Quarter Reports (History-Zoology), 1930-1931; 30 (Box 1)
  - 4. Winter Quarter Reports (Anatomy-Graphic Arts), 1930-1931; 30 (Box 1)
  - 5. Winter Quarter Reports (History-Zoology), 1930-1931; 30 (Box 1)
  - 6. Spring Quarter Reports (Anatomy - Graphic Arts), 1930-1931; 30 (Box 1)
  - 7. Spring Quarter Reports (History - Zoology)(refilmed for clarity on 35R), 1930-1931; 30 (Box 1)
  - 1. Advanced Senior Reports, 1930-1931; 31 (Box 1)
  - 2. Med Reports, 1929-1930, 1930-1931; 31 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer Quarter Reports, 1930-1931; 31 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1931-1932; 31 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports (Hist. - Poly Sci.), 1931-1932; 31 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports (Phych. - Zool), 1931-1932; 32 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1931-1932; 32 (Box 1)
  - 3. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1931-1932; 32 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1931-1932; 32 (Box 1)
  - 5. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1931-1932; 32 (Box 1)
  - 6. Advanced Senior Reports (Psych - Miles), 1931-1932; 32 (Box 1)
  - 1. Advanced Senior Reports (Public Speak. And expr.), 1931-1932; 33 (Box 1)
  - 2. Summer Quarter Reports, 1931-1932; 33 (Box 1)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Arts), 1932-1933; 33 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1932-1933; 33 (Box 1)
  - 5. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1932-1933; 33 (Box 1)
  - 6. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1932-1933; 33 (Box 1)
  - 7. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Educ. 184), 1932-1933; 33 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarter Reports (Educ. 190 - Graphic Art), 1932-1933; 34 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zoology), 1932-1933; 34 (Box 1)
  - 3. Advanced Senior Reports, 1932-1933; 34 (Box 1)
  - 4. Med. School Reports, 1932-1933; 34 (Box 1)
  - 5. Summer Quart. Qtr. Reports, 1932-1933; 34 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Educ. 228), 1933-1934; 34 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports (Educ. 234-Gr. Art), 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 2. Refilmed from 30 R: Psyc. 340-Pub.Sp.189-Rom.L.A113, 35 (Box 1)
  - 3. Autumn Quarter Reports (History-Zoology), 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 4. Winter Quarter Reports (Anatomy-Graphic Arts), 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 5. Senior Reports, 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 6. Senior Reports, 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 7. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool), 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 8. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. -P.E. 120 Sprague), 1933-1934; 35 (Box 1)
  - 5678 Out of order somewhat, 35 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (from Hyg.P.E.121 Bugge), 1933-1934; 36 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Records (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1933-1934; 36 (Box 1)
  - 3. Med. School Reports, 1933-1934; 36 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Quarter Reports, 1933-1934; 36 (Box 1)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1934-1935; 36 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Quarter Reports (Hist. - Phy. Ed.105), 1934-1935; 36 (Box 1)
  - Reflilmed for purpose of clarity (Hyg. And P.E.3 Pieces-Heilman), 36 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports (Phys. Ed. 105 - Slavic), 1934-1935; 37 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1934-1935; 37 (Box 1)
  - 3. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Slavic), 1934-1935; 37 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1934-1935; 37 (Box 1)
  - 5. Spring Quarter Reports, 1934-1935; 37 (Box 1)
  - 6. Advanced Senior Reports (Econ. 106), 1934-1935; 37 (Box 1)
  - 1. Advanced Senior Reports (from Econ. 107), 1934-1935; 38 (Box 1)
  - 2. Med. School Reports, 1934-1935; 38 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer Quarter Qtr. Reports, 1934-1935; 38 (Box 1)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1935-1936; 38 (Box 1)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Slavic), 1935-1936; 38 (Box 1)
  - 6. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - C.E. 101), 1935-1936; 38 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (C.E. 103 - Graphic Art), 1935-1936; 39 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Zool.), 1935-1936; 39 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1935-1936; 39 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Slavic), 1935-1936; 39 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports (to Mil.Sci.152), 1935-1936; 39 (Box 1)
  - Microdex markers #23 omitted, 39 (Box 1)
  - 1. Advanced Senior Reports (from Mil.Sci.152), 1935-1936; 40 (Box 1)
  - 2. Summer Quarter Reports, 1935-1936; 40 (Box 1)
  - 3. Med. School Reports, 1935-1936; 40 (Box 1)
  - 4. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anatomy-Gr. Art), 1936-1937; 40 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports (Hist. - Social Sci.), 1936-1937; 40 (Box 1)
  - 6. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Germ.Lang.B 1), 1936-1937; 40 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Ger.Lang.B1 - Gr. Art), 1936-1937; 41 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Soc. Sci.), 1936-1937; 41 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1936-1937; 41 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Slavic), 1936-1937; 41 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports, 1936-1937; 41 (Box 1)
  - 6. Med. School Reports (to Surgery-Winter), 1936-1937; 41 (Box 1)
  - 1. Med. School Reports, 1936-1937; 42 (Box 1)
  - 2. Summer Quarter Reports, 1936-1937; 42 (Box 1)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Arts), 1937-1938; 42 (Box 1)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1937-1938; 42 (Box 1)
  - 5. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1937-1938; 42 (Box 1)
  - 6. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Phys. Ed.121), 1937-1938; 42 (Box 1)
  - Last three sheets refilmed on 50 R for purpose of clarity (Adv. Swimming. Sprague), 42 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Phy.Ed.121-Speech), 1937-1938; 43 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - History), 1937-1938; 43 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Hgy. -Speech), 1937-1938; 43 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, 1937-1939; 43 (Box 1)
  - 5. Med. School Reports, 1937-1938; 43 (Box 1)
  - 6. Summer Quarter Reports (to Chem. 303), 1937-1938; 43 (Box 1)
  - 1. Summer Quarter Reports (From Classics A-1), 1937-1938; 44 (Box 1)
  - 2. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Hopkins Marine), 1938-1939; 44 (Box 1)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hyg. - Speech), 1938-1939; 44 (Box 1)
  - 4. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1938-1939; 44 (Box 1)
  - 5. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Phys.Ed.W 8), 1938-1939; 44 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Phys.Ed.W 58-Speech), 1938-1939; 45 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Qtr. Reports (Anat. -Gr. Art), 1938-1939; 45 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1938-1939; 45 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, Jun-39; 45 (Box 1)
  - 5. Med. School Reports (Med.404-Neurology), 1938-1939; 45 (Box 1)
  - 1. Aut. 34-35 Phs.Ed.Act. (Heilman-3 sheets), 46 (Box 1)
  - 2. Med. School Reports (from Med.404), 1938-1939; 46 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer Quarter Reports, 1938-1939; 46 (Box 1)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1939-1940; 46 (Box 1)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1939-1940; 46 (Box 1)
  - 6. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Geol.2), 1939-1940; 46 (Box 1)
  - Refilmed from R36 for purpose of clarity: Aut. 34-35 Phys.Ed.Act.3 Sheets, 46 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Geol.102-Gr. Art), 1939-1940; 47 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Gr. Art-Speech), 1939-1940; 47 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Graphic Art), 1939-1940; 47 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Quarter Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1939-1940; 47 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports (to Psych.199), 1939-1940; 47 (Box 1)
  - 1. Senior Reports (From Psych 213-Speech), 1939-1940; 48 (Box 1)
  - 2. Med. School Reports, 1939-1940; 48 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer Quarter Reports, 1939-1940; 48 (Box 1)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1940-1941; 48 (Box 1)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1940-1941; 48 (Box 1)
  - 6. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - English 2), 1940-1941; 48 (Box 1)
  - Med. 38-39 (Anaesthesia) filmed at beginning of Med. 39-40, 48 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Eng.2-Speech), 1940-1941; 49 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1940-1941; 49 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1940-1941; 49 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Qtr. Reports (Hist. - Speech), 1940-1941; 49 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports (to Relig.216), Jun-41; 49 (Box 1)
  - 1. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Adv. Sim.-Sprague) three sheets, 1937-1938; 50 (Box 1)
  - 2. Advanced Senior Reports (From Rom.Lang), Jun-41; 50 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer Quarter Reports, 1940-1941; 50 (Box 1)
  - 4. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Health M), 1941-1942; 50 (Box 1)
  - 5. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Health W - Speech), 1941-1942; 50 (Box 1)
  - 6. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Health M), 1941-1942; 50 (Box 1)
  - 7. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Health W. - Min. Engr.215), 1941-1942; 50 (Box 1)
  - #1 Refilmed for purpose of clarity, 50 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Min.Engr.216-Speech), 1941-1942; 51 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quater Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1941-1942; 51 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Qtr. Reports (Health - Speech), 1941-1942; 51 (Box 1)
  - 4. Advanced Senior Reports, 1941-1942; 51 (Box 1)
  - 5. Summer Quarter Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1941-1942; 51 (Box 1)
  - 6. Summer Quarter Reports (Health-Letter J.102), 1941-1942; 51 (Box 1)
  - 1. Summer Quarter Reports (Library-Speech), 1941-1942; 52 (Box 1)
  - 2. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Health M), 1942-1943; 52 (Box 1)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Health W - Speech), 1942-1943; 52 (Box 1)
  - 4. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1942-1943; 52 (Box 1)
  - 5. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Health W - Speech), 1942-1943; 52 (Box 1)
  - 6. Spring Qtr. Reports (Anat. - M.E. 236), 1942-1943; 52 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarter Reports (M.E. 240 - Gr. Art), 1942-1943; 53 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports (Health - A.S.T.P.), 1942-1943; 53 (Box 1)
  - 3. Senior Reports, 1942-1943; 53 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Quarter Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1942-1943; 53 (Box 1)
  - 5. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Hist. - A.S.T.P.), 1942-1943; 53 (Box 1)
  - 6. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - A.S.T.P. Mercer), 1943-1944; 53 (Box 1)
  - 1. Autumn Quarter Reports (ASTP 111 - Health Men), 1943-1944; 54 (Box 1)
  - 2. Autumn Quarter Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1943-1944; 54 (Box 1)
  - 3. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1943-1944; 54 (Box 1)
  - 4. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1943-1944; 54 (Box 1)
  - 5. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1943-1944; 54 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarter Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1943-1944; 55 (Box 1)
  - 2. Advanced Senior Reports, 1943-1944; 55 (Box 1)
  - 3. Summer Quarter Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1943-1944; 55 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Quarter Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1943-1944; 55 (Box 1)
  - 5. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1944-1945; 55 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Quarter Reports (Health Men - Speech), 1944-1945; 55 (Box 1)
  - 7. Winter Quarter Reports (Anat. - Classics B102), 1944-1945; 55 (Box 1)
  - 1. Winter Quarter Reports (Classic B113-Health M), 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 2. Winter Quarter Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 3. Spring Quarter Reports (Anat. - HealthM), 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 4. Spring Qtr. Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 5. Advanced Senior Reports, 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 6. Summer Quarter Reports (Anat. - Gr. Art), 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 7. Sum. Qtr. Reports (Health-Humanities-90B), 1944-1945; 56 (Box 1)
  - 1. Summer Quarter Reports (Humanities 150 - Speech), 1944-1945; 57 (Box 1)
  - 2. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Health M), 1945-1946; 57 (Box 1)
  - 3. Aut. Qtr. Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1945-1946; 57 (Box 1)
  - 4. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1945-1946; 57 (Box 1)
  - 5. Wint. Qtr. Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1945-1946; 57 (Box 1)
  - 6. Spring Qtr. Reports (Anat. - Educ.290), 1945-1946; 57 (Box 1)
  - 1. Spring Quarter Reports (Educ. 291-Health Men), 1945-1946; 58 (Box 1)
  - 2. Spring Quarter Reports (Health Women - Speech), 1945-1946; 58 (Box 1)
  - 3. Advanced Senior Reports, 1945-1946; 58 (Box 1)
  - 4. Summer Quarter Reports (Anat. - Health Men), 1945-1946; 58 (Box 1)
  - 5. Sum. Qtr. Reports (P.E. Women - Speech), 1946; 58 (Box 1)
  - 6. Autumn Quarter Reports (Anat. - Engineering), 1946-1947; 58 (Box 1)
  - 1. Supplementary Reports (2nd half reel), 85 (Box 1)
  - 2. Lists folled by Aaron, Miriam, 85 (Box 1)
  - 3. Allen, Joseph, 85 (Box 1)
  - 4. (ends) Azevedo, M.L., 85 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary GR. Sheets (Reel #ed 598 in error), 86 (Box 1)
  - 1. Baba, Masao, 86 (Box 1)
  - 2. Barritt, Clay, 86 (Box 1)
  - 3. Bent, Elizabeth Walsh, 86 (Box 1)
  - 4. Bloomfield, Anne, 86 (Box 1)
  - 5. Brandes, Charles, 86 (Box 1)
  - 6. Browning, Mary Emma, 86 (Box 1)
  - 7. Butterfield, H.G. (ends) Carlisle, Robt., 86 (Box 1)
  - 1. Carlsen, William F., 87 (Box 1)
  - 2. Chase, Fred C., 87 (Box 1)
  - 3. Cobb, Phil R., 87 (Box 1)
  - 4. Cordrey, Frank B., 87 (Box 1)
  - 5. Cummings, Charles Ward, 87 (Box 1)
  - 6. Dearing, Judith, 87 (Box 1)
  - 7. (ends) Dunlop, Florence, 87 (Box 1)
  - Reel numbered 599 in error, 87 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Grades, 88 (Box 1)
  - 1. Dunmire, Helene, 88 (Box 1)
  - 2. Elms, M.K., 88 (Box 1)
  - 3. Fennell, Victor D., 88 (Box 1)
  - 4. Ford, James Gregory, 88 (Box 1)
  - 5. Gabriel, Donald, 88 (Box 1)
  - 6. Gillespie, B.W., 88 (Box 1)
  - 7. (ends) Griswald, Robert, 88 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Reports, 89 (Box 1)
  - 1. Griswald, Sam, 89 (Box 1)
  - 2. Hammett, R.L., 89 (Box 1)
  - 3. Hauser, Henry P., 89 (Box 1)
  - 4. Herrmann, Edna, 89 (Box 1)
  - 5. Holbrook, Lettie D., 89 (Box 1)
  - 6. Hubbard, Mary E., 89 (Box 1)
  - 7. (ends) Johnson, Harry R., 89 (Box 1)
  - 1. Johnson, Harold E., 90 (Box 1)
  - 2. Kawaguchi, Tadashi M., 90 (Box 1)
  - 3. King, Rowland R., 90 (Box 1)
  - 4. Lacey, W. U., 90 (Box 1)
  - 5. Lee, Orrin E., 90 (Box 1)
  - 6. Little, William Lawson, 90 (Box 1)
  - 7. Lyons, Sam A. B., 90 (Box 1)
  - 8. (Ends) McKell, W.S., 90 (Box 1)
  - 1. McKellar, Donald, 91 (Box 1)
  - 2. Mainland, Gordon, 91 (Box 1)
  - 3. Matsumura, Kiyoshi, 91 (Box 1)
  - 4. Miller, Alfred A., 91 (Box 1)
  - 5. Moore, David, 91 (Box 1)
  - 6. (ends) Nichols, Elizabeth, 91 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Reports, 92 (Box 1)
  - 1. Nichols, Ernestine, 92 (Box 1)
  - 2. O'Neill, Thomas, 92 (Box 1)
  - 3. Patterson, Jack S., 92 (Box 1)
  - 4. Pickering, Loring, 92 (Box 1)
  - 5. Pronzoto, Mary, 92 (Box 1)
  - 6. Reed, Ian, 92 (Box 1)
  - 7. (ends) Ross, D. Campbell, 92 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Reports, 93 (Box 1)
  - 1. Ross, Dean, 93 (Box 1)
  - 2. Saunders, James F., 93 (Box 1)
  - 3. Segel, David, 93 (Box 1)
  - 4. Sibley, John T., 93 (Box 1)
  - 5. Smith, Julian, 93 (Box 1)
  - 6. Squire, Nancy Ann, 93 (Box 1)
  - 7. (ends) Sumpf, Robert, 93 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Reports, 94 (Box 1)
  - 1. Sun, C.Y., 94 (Box 1)
  - 2. Tenerello, Frank J., 94 (Box 1)
  - 3. Todd, Walter E., 94 (Box 1)
  - 4. Van Brocklin, Ralph M., 94 (Box 1)
  - 5. Wallace, William W., 94 (Box 1)
  - 6. Wells, David, 94 (Box 1)
  - 7. Wilde, F.L., 94 (Box 1)
  - (ends) Wilson, William A., 94 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Cards: A - CAD, 1 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Grade Changes: CAD - HEN, 2 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Grade Changes: HEN - MAX, 3 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Grade Changes: MAX - Robu, P., 4 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Grade Changes: Roch to Wilde, K., 5 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Grade Changes: Williams P - Wilde K, 6 (Box 1)
  - Nursing Records: Abe, Aiko - Zschokke, Ann, Oct-89; #7_89 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Doganis, Kyriakos - Ezra, Ann, Dec-91; 18 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Fabela, Angie K. - Fylstra, Mary Beth, Dec-91; 19 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Gabaldon R. Juan Jose - Goodwin, Susan, Dec-91; 20 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Goon, George - Gyori, Philip John, Dec-91; 21 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Ha, Chung Nim - Hegge, Osama H., Dec-91; 22 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Heggem, Richard A. - Howell, Timothy, Dec-91; 23 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Howenstein, Amy - Johsnon, William W., Dec-91; 24 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Johnston, Barbar - Kishimoto, Yoriko, Dec-91; 25 (Box 1)
  - Kishiyama Jeffrey - Lee, Lynton, Dec-91; 26 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Kishiyama, Jeffrey - Lee, Lynton, Jan-92; 26 (Box 1)
  - Grade Reports: Ma, Barry - McWhinney, Mark, Mar-92; 28 (Box 1)
  - End Quarter Reports, 1 (Box 2)
  - Spring Quarter 60/61 (Math, Art, Architecture Degree Candidates), 1 (Box 2)
  - Spring Quarter 60/61 (Econ, English, EL, 1st Year German), 1 (Box 2)
  - 1974 Reports, 1 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 17-Sep-75; 2 (Box 2)
  - Spring Quarter 60/61 (Eng, German), 2 (Box 2)
  - Summer Quarter 60/61 (Admin. Bus., History), 2 (Box 2)
  - Autumn Quarter 61/62 (CoEd PE, Admin, Arch), 2 (Box 2)
  - 1945 Reports, 2 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 18-Sep-75; 3 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 61/62 (Ae, Arch, Arch Design), 3 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 61/62 (Art, English), 3 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 61/62 (Geog, ELG), 3 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 61/62 (Admin., IE, AIRS, Eng, Art, Art of Asia), 3 (Box 2)
  - 1950 Reports, 3 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 18-Sep-75; 4 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 61/62 (Airs, Engl., Art, Geog, Mus, Stat, Law), 4 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 61/62 (Adm. Arch, Art, Phil), 4 (Box 2)
  - 1958 Reports, 4 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 18-Sep-75; 5 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 61/62 (Art-Phil, Phsc-Pete, Admin-Me, Airs-Hist, Hum-Soc), 5 (Box 2)
  - 1943 Reports, 5 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 18-Sep-75; 6 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 61/62 (Hum-Soc, Phys), 6 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 61/62 (Fri, Hist), 6 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 62/63 (Admin-EM, Engr-CLC), 6 (Box 2)
  - 1750 Reports, 6 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 19-Sep-75; 7 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 62/63 (Comm-Hist, Hum-Phys, Pol Sci-SRS), 7 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 62/63 (Admin,EE-Chem, Hist, Econ), 7 (Box 2)
  - 1932 Reports, 7 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 19-Sep-75; 8 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 62/63 (Hist, Econ, Math, Mus, Stat), 8 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 62/63 (Admin, Asia, Math), 8 (Box 2)
  - 1942 Reports, 8 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Sep-75; 9 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 62/63 (Asia, Math, ELG, Admin, EES, Comm, Hist, Poli Sci), 9 (Box 2)
  - 1969 Reports, 9 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Sep-75; 10 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 62/63 (Pols), 10 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 62/63 (Hist), 10 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr 63/64 (Admin, Comm, Hist), 10 (Box 2)
  - 1933 Reports, 10 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Sep-75; 11 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 63/64 (Comm, Hist, Eur, Phs, Pols), 11 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 63/64 (Admin, Che, Asia, Bio), 11 (Box 2)
  - 1956 Reports, 11 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Sep-75; 12 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 63/64 (Hist, Ling, Mus, Phrm, Phs), 12 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 63/64 (Admin, ME, Math, Pols, Mus), 12 (Box 2)
  - 1970 Reports, 12 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 22-Sep-75; 13 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 63/64 (Pols, Mus, SSCI, Admin, Comm, Hist, Hum, Phys, Pols, Anat), 13 (Box 2)
  - 1960 Reports, 13 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 23-Sep-75; 14 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 63/64 (Pols, Anat), 14 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 63/64 (Anth), 14 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 64/65 (CE, CLC, Comm, Hist), 14 (Box 2)
  - 1924 Reports, 14 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Sep-75; 15A (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 64/65 (Comm, Hist. Hum, Phys, Pols), 15A (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 64/65 (EE, CLC), 15A (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. (Art, CoEd), 15A (Box 2)
  - 1920 Reports, 15A (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 15-Oct-75; 15B (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 64/65 (Comm, Hist, Hum, Pols, Psyc, SRC), 15B (Box 2)
  - 1240 Reports, 15B (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Sep-75; 16 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 64/65 (Admin, Art, Ling, Mus, EES, EM, CLT, Comm, Hist, Engl, Amer Lit), 16 (Box 2)
  - 1941 Reports, 16 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Sep-75; 17 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 64/65 (Comm, Hist, Engl, Hum, Phsy, Pols), 17 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 64/65 (Geog), 17 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 65/66 (PE, Golf), 17 (Box 2)
  - 1935 copies, 17 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Sep-75; 18 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 65/66 (PE, EE, Comm, Hist, Hum, Phys, Pols), 18 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 65/66 (CE, EDUC), 18 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Sep-75; 19 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 65/66 (CE, EDUC, EE, CL, Comm, Hist, Hum, Pys, Pol, Geog), 19 (Box 2)
  - 1920 Reports, 19 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Sep-75; 20 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 65/66 (Pols), 20 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 65/66 (ME, ELA, ELP, CE, CLC, German), 20 (Box 2)
  - 1910 Reports, 20 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Sep-75; 21 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 65/66 (ELG, German, Comm, Hum, Math, Phys, Pols), 21 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 65/66 (Engl, Geog, Stat), 21 (Box 2)
  - 1929 Reports, 21 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Sep-75; 22 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 65/66 (Geog, Stat), 22 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 66/67 (EE), 22 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 66/67 (CE, EE, JPN Lit), 22 (Box 2)
  - 1922 Reports, 22 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 16-Oct-75; 23 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 66/67 (Comm, Hum, Math, Phys, Pols), 23 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 66/67 (EE, ALJ, JPN Lit, Comm, Hum, Mah, German), 23 (Box 2)
  - 1950 Reports, 23 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 16-Oct-75; 24 (Box 2)
  - Win. Qtr. 66/67 (Math, Pnys, Eur Lit, Pols), 24 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 66/67 (ME, EES, ELA, Nurs, Pub Hlth), 24 (Box 2)
  - 1888 Reports, 24 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Nov-75; 25 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 66/67 (ELP, Phth, CE, Comm, Hum, Math, Phys, Pols, Law), 25 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 24-Nov-75; 26 (Box 2)
  - Spr. Qtr. 66/67 (Law), 26 (Box 2)
  - Sum. Qtr. 66/67 (EE, Hum, Math, BioP, Econ, Engl), 26 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 67/68 (HIN, CoEd), 26 (Box 2)
  - End Quarter Reports, 25-Nov-75; 27 (Box 2)
  - Aut. Qtr. 67/68 (HIN, Coed, AA, ALJ, BIOL, Hum, Hist, Psyc, Pols, Mine, Phys Chem), 27 (Box 2)
  - 1912 Reports, 27 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Abbott, William L. - Azzaretto, Emanuele, Dec-91; 11 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Baar, Roger - Berry, Roderick R., Dec-91; 12 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Berryhill, Bruce R. - Brimelow, Peter, Dec-91; 13 (Box 2)
  - Grade Cards 1970-1989: Briner, Clifton - Carlos, Lisandra, Dec-91; 14 (Box 2)